<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Max Aantjes</title>
    <link>https://maxaantjes.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Max Aantjes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://maxaantjes.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The transition from Private to Public Education in Ecuador: what does it mean?</title>
      <link>https://maxaantjes.github.io/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxaantjes.github.io/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>At the end of June, the IADB reported that public education enrolment in the Ecuadorian coastal provinces had increased with 6.5% (Olson, 2020). Last week, Ecuavisa, a major Ecuadorian Television Network reported that over 150 thousand students nationwide have transitioned from private to public institutions (Ecuavisa, 2020). This post provides a brief analysis of the potential effect of this transition in Ecuador and explores policy recommendations.
This apparent fall in private education enrolment was expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitalisation of the Ecuadorian Education System during Covid-19: an Exploratory Analysis of three Factors of Exclusion</title>
      <link>https://maxaantjes.github.io/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxaantjes.github.io/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>The world is facing an unparalleled education crisis. At the time of writing, still over a billion learners in 143 countries area affected by school closures (UNESCO, 2020). In one of these countries, Ecuador, the government has responded by rapidly digitalising its education system. Despite these efforts, some columnists have publicly started to question the fairness of this approach (Constante, 2020). My brief analysis of household survey data collected in 2019 strengthens such worries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>